A Finding Aid to the Joseph Lindon Smith Papers, 1647-1965, bulk 1873-1965, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Letters, 1768-1965; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; (Box 1-4, OV 11; 3.5 linear feet)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "D" - "F,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "G,", undated; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "H" - "J,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "K" - "M,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "N" - "R,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "S,", undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "T" - "Z,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Letters, 1768-1848; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Letters, 1873-1882; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Letters, 1883; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 21-23)
  - Letters, 1884; Archival Resource Key; (12 folders) (Box 1, Folder 24-35)
  - Letters, 1885; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 1, Folder 36-40)
  - Letters, 1886-1890; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Letters, 1891; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 42-44)
  - Letters, 1892; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 45-46)
  - Letters, 1893; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 47-49)
  - Letters, 1894; Archival Resource Key; (10 folders) (Box 1, Folder 50-59)
  - Letters, 1895; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 60-62)
  - Letters, 1896; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 1, Folder 63-67)
  - Letters, 1897; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders) (Box 1, Folder 68-73)
  - Letters, 1898; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 1, Folder 74-77)
  - Letters, 1899; Archival Resource Key; (11 folders) (Box 1, Folder 78-88)
  - Letters, 1900; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 89-91)
  - Letters, 1901; Archival Resource Key; (8 folders) (Box 1, Folder 92-99)
  - Letters, 1902; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Letters, 1903; Archival Resource Key; (9 folders) (Box 2, Folder 4-12)
  - Letters, 1904; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Letters, 1905; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - Letters, 1906; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - Letters, 1907; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
  - Letters, 1908; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 20-23)
  - Letters, 1909; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 2, Folder 24-28)
  - Letters, 1910; Archival Resource Key; (8 folders) (Box 2, Folder 29-36)
  - Letters, 1911; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 37-40)
  - Letters, 1912; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 41-43)
  - Letters, 1913; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 44-46)
  - Letters, 1914; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 47-50)
  - Letters, 1915; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 51-54)
  - Letters, 1916; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 55-58)
  - Letters, 1917; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 59-61)
  - Letters, 1918; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 62-64)
  - Letters, 1919; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 65-66)
  - Letters, 1920; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 67-68)
  - Letters, 1921; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 69-71)
  - Letters, 1922; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 72-74)
  - Letters, 1923; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Letters, 1924; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders; Oversized Material Housed in OV 11) (Box 3, Folder 4-7)
  - Letters, 1925; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Letters, 1926; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Letters, 1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Letters, 1928; Archival Resource Key; (8 folders) (Box 3, Folder 11-18)
  - Letters, 1929; Archival Resource Key; (7 folders) (Box 3, Folder 19-25)
  - Letters, 1930; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 26-29)
  - Letters, 1931; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 30-34)
  - Letters, 1932; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 35-38)
  - Letters, 1933; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
  - Letters, 1934; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 41-42)
  - Letters, 1935; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 43-45)
  - Letters, 1936; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 46-49)
  - Letters, 1937; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 50-52)
  - Letters, 1938; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 53-54)
  - Letters, 1939; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 3, Folder 55-58)
  - Letters, 1940; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders) (Box 3, Folder 59-64)
  - Letters, 1941; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 65-69)
  - Letters, 1942; Archival Resource Key; (9 folders) (Box 3, Folder 70-78)
  - Letters, 1943; Archival Resource Key; (9 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-9)
  - Letters, 1944; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 10-12)
  - Letters, 1945; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 13-15)
  - Letters, 1946; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
  - Letters, 1947; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
  - Letters, 1948; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 4, Folder 20-23)
  - Letters, 1949; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 24-26)
  - Letters, 1950; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 27-29)
  - Letters, 1951-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Letters, 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Letters, 1955-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Letters, 1961-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Oversized Drawing of Plan of The Oaks Pool Enclosed in Letter, 1924; Archival Resource Key; (from Box 3, Folder 7) (Oversize 11)
- Diaries, 1904-1949; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; (Box 4; 11 folders)
  There are seven diaries written by Joseph Lindon Smith and two by Corinna Smith during their travels in Egypt, Europe, and New Mexico.
  - Diary 1: Egypt, 1904-1905; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 34-35)
  - Diary 2: Egypt, 1906-1907; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Diary 3: Europe, 1917; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Diary 4: Europe, 1918; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 38-39)
  - Diary 5: Europe, 1918-1919; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Diary 6: New Mexico, 1926; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Diary 7: Persia (Persepolis), 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Diary 8 by Corinna Putnam Smith: Beiram, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Diary 9 by Corinna Putnam Smith: Egypt, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Personal Business Records, 1647-1959; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; (Box 4, 10; 11 folders)
  Personal business records are found for both the Smith and Putnam families and for Joseph Lindon Smith, Corinna Smith, and their daughter Lois Smith. These include contracts, price lists, lists of securities, and miscellaneous receipts.
  - Legal Documents and Receipts for the Smith and Putnam Ancestors, 1647-1882, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
  - Price Lists, 1894-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Contract; Certificate of Shares in The Chelsea Pottery, 1895-1897; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1902-1959; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 49-50)
  - Legal Documents Concerning Lois Lindon Smith, 1929-1936; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 51-52)
  - Records of Stocks and Other Assets, 1938-1953; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders; Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 4, Folder 53-55)
  - Oversized Statements of Trusteeship, 1951-1953; Archival Resource Key; from Box 4, Folder 55 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Notes and Writings, 1783-1963; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; (Box 4-6; 2.0 linear feet)
  Notes and writings include engagement calendars, notebooks, lists of art work, lecture notes, minutes of meetings, notes on family history and travel, and numerous miscellaneous typescripts by the Smiths and others of essays and anecdotes about art, culture, travel, and many other topics. Also found are drafts for "Egypt - My Winter Home."
  - Engagement Calendar, 1914; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Engagement Calendar, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Notebook 1, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Notebook 2, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Notebook 3, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Notebook 4, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Notebook 5, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Notebook 6, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Notes on Asia, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Notes on the Careers of Maya Archaeologists, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Notes on Egypt, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 66-67)
  - Notes by Corinna Smith on "Egyptian Religion,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Notes on Cecil Firth's Excavations, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Notes on Mexico and Central America, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Notes on Persia, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Notes on George Reisner, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 72-73)
  - Notes on Writers in Arabic, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Autograph of Kit Carson; Autograph of Finnish Folk Singer Selma Borg, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Lists of Art Work, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Lists of Art Work, 1931-1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Notes on Family History, 1945-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Minutes of Meeting of Archeological Club, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Notes Describing Karnak, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Card File of Egyptian Art Work, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Remarks by Abd Essalam Hussein Delivered at the United States National Sculpture Society, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Broadcast for Egyptian Minister of Foreign Affairs, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Notes on Sakkara, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Minutes of Meeting Concerning Recommendations to Trustees, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lecture Notes for "Journey Into the Past" for the Metropolitan Museum, 1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Meeting of International Cooperation Administration, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Minutes of Meeting of the American Research Center in Egypt, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Anecdotes, undated; Archival Resource Key; (9 folders) (Box 5, Folder 11-19)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1915-1946, undated; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 5, Folder 20-23)
  - Typescript "A Letter Addressed to Students of the Art of Painting and to his Professional Brethern,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Manuscript "Amman and Air Force,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Typescripts "The Dissenting Shi'a Sect" and "The Dream,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Typescripts "Hadiths" and "Maya Civilization,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Poems, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Manuscripts for Lectures on Portrait Painting, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Typescript "Three Dublin Artists,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Typescript "Colored Statues" Describing Events in 1891, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Greece in 1894, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Typescript "Primitive Travel" Describing Events in 1898, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Typescript "Quirigua and Copan" Describing Events in 1900; Typescript "With the Carnegie Staff at Chichen,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Typescript "The Sarcophagus Found at Sidon" Describing Events in 1900, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Typescript "Baalbek" Describing Events in 1900; Typescripts "Palmyra" and "Petra" Describing Events in 1930, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Japan in 1901, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Japan in 1901 and 1910, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Typescript "Visits to Italy and England" Describing Events in 1907, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Manuscript Describing Travel to Egypt in 1909, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Typescript "A Visit to London" Describing Events in 1909, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to China in 1910, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Typescripts "The Ypres Salient," "Fort Douaumont," and "Fort De Vaux" Describing Events in 1918, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Typescript Describing Events in World War I, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Typescript "Things Done by Mr. Smith,", 1918; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Typescript "Notes for Mr. Smith,", 1918; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Typescript "Economic Crisis in Germany in October 1920,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Typescript "Siam" Describing Events in 1921, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Manuscript "the Dieng Plateau" Describing Events in 1921, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Java in 1921, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Bankok in 1921 and to Canton in 1923, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Typescript Describing Travel to Mexico in 1926, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Typescript "Fido,", 1926; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Manuscript "Excavations at Ur" Describing Events in 1930, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Typescript "Ur of the Chaldees and Other Way Stations" Describing Events in 1930, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Manuscript "Conflicting Ideas in Egypt of Today" Describing Events in 1931, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Typescripts "The Trip to Persepolis" Describing Events in 1935, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 57-58)
  - Manuscript Describing Travel to Egypt, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Typescript "Experience in Luxor" Describing Events in 1939, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Typescript "Journal Abydos" Describing Events in 1939, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 61-62)
  - Typescript for Lecture on Egypt for Bryn Mawr Benefit, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Report on Paintings of Sculpture and Architectural Details of the Ruins of Chichenitza, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Manuscript of Fund-Raising Address for the U.S.O., 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Typescript "Sesostris Shrine at Karnak,", 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Manuscript Describing Travel to Egypt, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Transcript of Lecture on Egypt for Visiting Committee on Semitic and Egyptian Civilizations, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Report to Visiting Committee of Egyptian Department, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Typescript "The 'New' Egypt,", 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Typescript of Address to the Smithsonian Institution, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Typescript 1: "Egypt: My Winter Home,", 1950; Archival Resource Key; (12 folders) (Box 5, Folder 72-83)
  - Typescript 2: "Egypt: My Winter Home,", 1950; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 5, Folder 84-86)
  - Typescript 3: "Egypt: My Winter Home,", 1950; Archival Resource Key; (19 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-19)
  - Miscellaneous Typescript Fragments, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Typescript "Joseph Lindon Smith" by Unidentified Author, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Typescript "Joseph Lindon Smith - In Memorium" by Unidentified Author, 1950-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author Describing Travel to the Southwest United States, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Typescript "Garibaldi's Chapel" by Unidentified Author, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Manuscript "Gleanings" by Unidentified Author, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author Concerning Gouda, the Shikari, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Typescript by Unidenfied Author Concerning Mark Twain's First Summer in Dublin, 1905; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Report Concerning Paul Cravath's Visit to Persepolis by the Field Director of the Iranian Expedition, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Typescript by Unidentified Author Concerning the British in Egypt in 1945, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Poems by Claude M. Fuess, 1933-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Manuscript Concerning George Yarnell by Lois Anna Greene, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Manuscript "The Hallucinations of Grandfather Chad" by Lois Anna Greene, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Typescript "A Painter of Ancient Masterpieces: Joseph Lindon Smith" by Anne Webb Karnaghan, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Poem "Our Mudir" by Mahmud, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Poems by Rebecca London Malicheff, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Typescript "Studies in Nietzschean Cosmology" by George Morgan, 1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Typescript "The Ancient Maya" by Sylvanus G. Morley, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Manuscript "Description of a Fire Dance on the Navajo Reservation at Nara" by Frances Smith Otis, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Typescript "An Artist's Unique Estate at Dublin Lake, Dublin, N.H." by Harris Walter Reynolds, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Manuscript Concerning Travel to Asia by Denman Ross, 1923; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Manuscript "The Dying Sayings of John Jencks" Copied by Chad Smith, 1783; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Poems by Emma Greenleaf Smith, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Typescript "Madonna Del Fieno" by Hermann Voss, W. Bode, and Prof. Fischel, 1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Typescript "Eulogy of the Dog" by George Graham Vest, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Poems, 1886-1947, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 45-46)
  - Miscellaneous Writings by Others, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Theatrical Production Files, 1897-1950; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; (Box 6-7, 10; 1.2 linear feet)
  These files contain letters, notes, scripts, printed material, and photographs concerning plays, pageants, and masques written and/or produced by the Smiths for benefits, dedication, or anniversary celebrations. A notebook "Grandma Smith's Teatro Bambino" contains 2 photographs, a dedication ode by Thomas Wentworth Higginson, and a hand-written script.
  - Notebook "Grandma Smith's Teatro Bambino,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Script for Play about the Spirit in the Fountain by Grandma Smith, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Untitled Play Scripts, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 50-51)
  - Script for Andover Pageant, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Script for Play The Astrologer, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Script for Play Birds of a Feather, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Script for the "Buccaneer Play,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Script for the "Christmas Play,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Script for the "Circus Play,", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Script for Play The Columns of Catlin, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Script for Play The Departure of Doris, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Script for Play Flora Enshrined, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Script for Play How to Adventure, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Script for Play The King of Kurosaki, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Script for Play The Lay of the Last Egg, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Script for Play The Legasee of the Hawaiian Buried Treasure, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Script for Play Mexican Fiesta, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Script for Play Monadnock Invaded, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Script for Play Old Gobblegain, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Script for Play Over the Rainbow, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Introductory Remarks for Dance Performance by Sarita and Riccardo Romero, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Script for Play A Shah of Persia, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Script for Play The Silence of the Harp, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Script for Play The Witch's Trunk, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Programs for Play Alice in Wonderland, 1897; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Script for Play Houri Kuri and Hurri Kurri, 1898; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Script for Play Danjuro No Tanjobi, 1904; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Script for Watteau Fete, 1906; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Script for Play Jack Frost in Midsummer, 1908-1949; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized Material Housed in Box 10) (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Script for Play The Enchanted Forest, 1909; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Program for Pantomime and Dance Traumeswirren ("Dream Fancies"), 1909; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Script for the "Chinese Play,", 1911; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - File for the Lancaster Pageant, 1912; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - File for the Pageant at Milton, 1912; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)